Narrator: 28
A: an accountant
Narrator: 26
B: an actor
Narrator: 2
A: an administrator
Narrator: 14
B: an architect
Narrator: 7
A: a chef
Narrator: 27
B: a cleaner
Narrator: 6
A: a construction worker
Narrator: 4
B: a dentist
Narrator: 17
A: a doctor
Narrator: 8
B: an engineer
Narrator: 11
A: a factory worker
Narrator: 22
B: a flight attendant
Narrator: 30
A: a guide
Narrator: 19
B: a hair stylist
Narrator: 10
A: a journalist
Narrator: 12
B: a lawyer
Narrator: 1
A: a manager
Narrator: 16
B: a model
Narrator: 18
A: a musician
Narrator: 5
B: a nurse
Narrator: 21
A: a pilot
Narrator: 23
B: a police officer
Narrator: 24
A: a receptionist
Narrator: 15
B: a salesperson
Narrator: 20
A: a server
Narrator: 13
A: a soccer player
Narrator: 9
B: a soldier
Narrator: 29
A: a taxi driver
Narrator: 25
B: a teacher
Narrator: 3
A: a vet